First day of school, get ready with me
for the car line. I'm ready.
>> Blush, blush. I don't really know.
>> Dance, these girls.
>> Look at what I got.
It's the moisturizer and bronzer drops
like half and half.
>> Pump, pump, pump, pump, pump. That's a
lot of time.
>> See, that's a lot. My mom's going to
have to use a lot of this. It turns out
really good though and the moisturizer
feels so nice on your skin.
>> Oh, there. Oh, I love the bronze right
away. Okay, how excited are you for
school on a scale of 1 to 10?
Oh, I don't know what I'll do. I guess
after you leave, maybe I'll walk on the
treadmill.
>> Oh my gosh, don't start this. I don't
know where my blush and eyeliner went.
And it's right here.
And now I'm doing my eyelash curling.
>> What's your favorite subject?
>> My favorites are either like reading or
writing.
>> Oh.
>> Sometimes I do my makeup and hair at the
same time. So that goes a little faster.
>> Well, when you have a hair stylist. So
Harper has waffles and this is the chef,
our private chef.
>> The street lights on, it's too early for
this. Okay, backpack
>> Amazon.
>> Diet Coke from Five
>> Okay, that's
>> water bottle
>> Amazon.
>> Can I Target? Emery edit sweatshirt from
Target.
>> New shoes, Nike.
>> Nike and a Kindersport.
>> AND THEN MY FIT CHECK. MY SHIRT from
Amazon, pants are from Amazon, my socks
are from Amazon and my shoes are from
Nike.
>> Hi.